<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 *  Copyright (c) 2014  Fundación TECNALIA Research & Innovation
 *  
 *  Licensed under the MIT license:
 *
 *  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
 *  of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
 *  in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
 *  to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sub-license, and/or sell
 *  copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
 *  furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
 *
 *  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
 *  all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
 *
 *  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
 *  IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
 *  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
 *  AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
 *  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
 *  OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
 *  THE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Contributors: Leire Orue-Echevarria Arrieta
 * Initially developed in the context of ARTIST EU project www.artist-project.eu
-->
<cheatsheet
      title="Value proposition">
   <intro>
      <description>
         Study the needs of the customers you are targeting to, their motivation, their perspectives, etc. The main idea is to understand why they would buy your service and not others. This can be done by interviews, surveys or observation. Once that is clear, explain what the added value of this application is with respect to its competitor. This can be, later on, your sales pitch argument.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Identify and analyse the customers’ needs and motivation">
      <description>
         Try to understand which is your target market and why each one of them would buy your product.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title = "Define the functionalities that need to be delivered to each customer segment in order to solve their needs">
      <description>
      If you have identified different market segments and different value propositions for each one of them, you should delimit what you will offer distinctively to each target group. This means, for instance, that the number of functionalities may vary depending on the target group. This can also vary if you decide to apply a tiered business model (e.g. regular user, professional user, enterprise user, etc.).
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
        title = "Define the value delivered to each customer segment">
      <description>
      Once the customers’ needs for each market segment and the corresponding functionalities to be provided, describe the value proposition specific for each of these segments. 
Some of the questions you need to be able to answer: What is the added value of this service compared to the one that my competitors are already providing? What am I offering that the others are not?
Tip: The value proposition must include what the service is aimed for and how it is different from the competitors. In addition to that, strategic definition of the value proposition, it is recommended to include for each service, the related technical information about the service offerings (capabilities, interface definitions including available service operations and pricing information)
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
