<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><AnswerList><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>O1</code><question>Do you have a monitoring component to monitor the usage  of the your SaaS applications by the consumers?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>BO3</code><question>Do you have a billing component?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Private Cloud</answer><code>OT3</code><question>Where?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Simultaneous users -Time, -Transaction (DB queries, storage, …), -Feature (modules, functionality)</answer><code>P1</code><question>Which pricing model do you have?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Select and purchase of cloud service (s) from one or more cloud service providers</answer><code>BS1</code><question>Do you plan to...</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Request of audit reports on the service(s) and the service provider(s), both before a purchase is completed and also periodically once the service is in use</answer><code>BS1</code><question>Do you plan to...</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Handling both financial and technical aspects of the services</answer><code>BS2</code><question>Does the management of your business plan involve</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Management of contracts and SLAs</answer><code>BS2</code><question>Does the management of your business plan involve</question></Answers><Answers><answer>The receipt of payments from the cloud provider and their accounting</answer><code>FM1</code><question>Does your financial processing management involve...</question></Answers><Answers><answer>The financial relationships with providers are not managed in a systematic way</answer><code>FM1</code><question>Does your financial processing management involve...</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Entitlements</answer><code>AM1</code><question>Does your account management procedure provide capabilities for managing cloud service customer relationships, including</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Cloud service customer data</answer><code>AM1</code><question>Does your account management procedure provide capabilities for managing cloud service customer relationships, including</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Plus a set of capabilities for the management of the content of the catalogue which are available to staff of the cloud service provider</answer><code>PC1</code><question>Do you have a Product catalogue that provides capabilities for cloud service customers</question></Answers><Answers><answer>There is no product/service catalogue</answer><code>PC1</code><question>Do you have a Product catalogue that provides capabilities for cloud service customers</question></Answers><Answers><answer>There is a defined process to measure customer satisfaction, but its implementation is not systematic</answer><code>CR3</code><question>Is customer satisfaction measured in any way?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>FP1</code><question>Is it defined how and when the use of the services should be metering?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>FP2</code><question>Are defined the pricing schedules (when, which discounts…) in the contract with the customer?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>FP3</code><question>The billing process is an automatic or non-automatic process that has into account the metering of the use of the services and the rating according to the contract with the customer?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>FP4</code><question>Is there a monitoring with the account manager in order to check that the payments from the customer are according to the invoices</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>SLA1</code><question>Is there a service level agreement (SLA-Service Level Agreement) that defines the services provided, as agreed between the service provider and the client?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>SLA3</code><question>If the service provided depends, to some extent, on external suppliers, do you have an underpinning agreement?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>SLA4</code><question>Do you periodically review the SLA definitions/conditions and the underpinning agreement?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Service levels are monitored but not in a systematic way</answer><code>SLA5</code><question>During the service provisioning do you regularly review the service levels committed?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>No control or review the levels of service provided</answer><code>SLA5</code><question>During the service provisioning do you regularly review the service levels committed?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>There is a mechanism for informing of the problem and the actions to carried out</answer><code>SLA6</code><question>Is there a mechanism in place to communicate the non-compliance with the SLA? </question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>CP1</code><question>Do you have formalized the agreement with the cloud provider in any way </question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>CP2</code><question>Do you monitor in a systematic way the fulfilment of the conditions and characteristics defined by the agreement?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>There is no agreement or it is not monitored</answer><code>CP3</code><question>Do you report to the cloud provider the non-fulfilment in order to assure the correct operation of cloud service?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>DP1</code><question>Do you have defined a development process for this kind of applications?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>No</answer><code>DP2</code><question>If yes, is the process you have defined an agile process?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>DP4</code><question>Do you have a defined procedure where update mechanisms and frequency are defined? (once a year, every 6 months, persons/roles who update …)</question></Answers><Answers><answer>No</answer><code>DP6</code><question>Do you have a maintenance process?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Define new roles (i.e Service delivery management)</answer><code>RA1</code><question>Select in the following list those activities you have done in order to adapt the roles of you organization to be cloud compliant</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Define the responsibilities for the new and existing ones</answer><code>RA1</code><question>Select in the following list those activities you have done in order to adapt the roles of you organization to be cloud compliant</question></Answers><Answers><answer>To the affected people their new activities and responsibilities</answer><code>RA2</code><question>Have you communicated the changes about roles?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Prepare a training plan</answer><code>RA3</code><question>Which of the following actions do you carry out for training the affected people? </question></Answers><Answers><answer>Train those people who are going to be assigned to the new or modified roles.</answer><code>RA3</code><question>Which of the following actions do you carry out for training the affected people? </question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>OT6</code><question>Do you know the performance profile of the application ?</question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>OT7</code><question>Does your application interoperate with any external tool? </question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>OT8</code><question>Are unit tests of the legacy application available? </question></Answers><Answers><answer>Yes</answer><code>CR41</code><question>Do you have a mechanism to record and solve the incidences? </question></Answers></AnswerList>