<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 *  Copyright (c) 2014 Institute of Communication and Computer Systems (ICCS) - National Technical University of Athens (NTUA)
 *  
 *  Licensed under the MIT license:
 *
 *  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
 *  of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
 *  in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
 *  to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sub-license, and/or sell
 *  copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
 *  furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
 *
 *  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
 *  all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
 *
 *  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
 *  IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
 *  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
 *  AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
 *  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
 *  OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
 *  THE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Contributors: Kleopatra Konstanteli
-->
<cheatsheet
      title="Perform maturity assessment">
   <intro>
      <description>
         <b>Use the Maturity Assessment Tool (MAT) to analyze the application to be migrated in order to characterize the business situation of the current legacy application as well as the characteristics that the migrated application should have under the business perspective.</b>
      </description>
   </intro> 
    
   <item
         title="Open MAT in a web browser">
      <description>
         <b> </b>
      </description>
      <!--command
            required="true"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.browser.openBrowser(url=http://ip:port/mat/)"/--> 
   </item>
    
   <item
         title="Login into MAT">
      <description>
         <b>Login into MAT by providing a valid login and password combination and pressing the “Accept” button. If you don't have an account, click on the “Create New User” button to create one. In this window the user has to fill in the formulary and press the “Create User” button. The fields with and (*) are mandatory.</b>
      </description>
   </item>
   
   <item
         title="Select dimension and scope of the questionnaire">
      <description>
         <b>In the dimension selection page that appears after login, select a dimension from the available ones (business, process, and technical) and the scope of the questionnaire (current situation, future situation)</b>
      </description>
   </item>
  
   <item	
  	  title="View available categories"> 
      <description>
         <b>Once the dimension and the scope are selected, the category window is opened. In this window you can view all the categories to be evaluated for a certain dimension/scope. Here the current status of the score achieved (based on the current status of the questionnaire that is the answers already provided) and the maximum score for each of the areas inside a dimension are presented. Also, the total score per dimension is showed.</b>
      </description>
   </item>
   
   <item	
  	  title="Fill in questionnaires"> 
      <description>
         <b>Clicking in any category will allow you to access the Question window, where you need to answer the relevant questionnaire. Clicking on “Save Answers” button will store your answers, so when you enter the questionnaire again, the questions will be answered. If the “Cancel” button is clicked, the previous windows will appear without saving changes.</b>
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
