<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="ARTIST Methodology Process Tool Pre-Migration Phase">
   <taskGroup kind="set" name="Pre-Migration Group" skip="false">
      <intro>
         <b>This cheat sheet demonstrates how to use the ARTIST tools through the Methodology Process Tool (MPT) to migrate your project to the Cloud.</b>
      </intro>
      <onCompletion>
         <b>Conclusion</b>
      </onCompletion>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Perform maturity assessment" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Use the Maturity Assessment Tool (MAT) to analyze the application to be migrated in order to characterize the business situation of the current legacy application as well as the characteristics that the migrated application should have under the business perspective</b>
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b> </b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="premigration/maturity_assessment_simplev2.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Perform business feasibility analysis" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>This cheat sheet shows how to create a new Business Scenario Workbench (BSW) project to define Business Models.</b>
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>A Business Scenario Workbench Project with a Business Model presenting various diagrams has been created.</b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="premigration/business_feasibility_updated_simple.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Perform technical feasibility analysis" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Evaluate the technical situation of the application to be migrated.</b>
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>The results from the technical feasibility analysis are included in the report from the TFT. </b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="premigration/technical_feasibility_simple.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Evaluate changes on the initial parameters" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Evaluate if due to the results obtained in the previous tasks you want to re-do the pre-migration changing some parameters related to the desired situation.</b>
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>  </b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="premigration/evaluate_changes_simple.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Configure methodology" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Use MPT to customize the ARTIST Methodology.</b>
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>At the end of this task, the ARTIST Methodology has been customized according to the maturity, technical and business analysis results of the ARTIST Tools.</b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="premigration/conf_mpt_simple.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
