<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 *  Copyright (c) 2014 - 2015 Fundación TECNALIA Research & Innovation
 *  
 *  Licensed under the MIT license:
 *
 *  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
 *  of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
 *  in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
 *  to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sub-license, and/or sell
 *  copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
 *  furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
 *
 *  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
 *  all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
 *
 *  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
 *  IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
 *  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
 *  AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
 *  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
 *  OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
 *  THE SOFTWARE.
 *
 * Contributors: Marisa Escalante Martinez (Tecnalia)
 * Initially developed in the context of ARTIST EU project www.artist-project.eu
-->
<cheatsheet
      title="SLAMP - SLA Management Process Task">
   <intro>
      <description>
         The goal of SLA management process is to ensure that an agreed level of IT services is provide for all current IT services and that the future services are delivered to agreed achievable targets. SLA management process should ensure that all operational services and their performance are measured in a consistent, professional manner throughout the IT organization, and that the services and the reports produced, meet the needs of the business and customers.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="SLAMP.A1 – Determine SLA Framework">
      <description>
         This activity should design the most appropriate SLA structure to ensure that all the services and all the customers are covered in a manner best suited to the organization’s needs
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="SLAMP.A2 - Determine, document and agree requirements for existing and new services">
      <description>
         All those issues included in the SLA framework should be determined and documented and agreed for each provided service.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="SLAMP.A3 - Review underpinning agreements">
      <description>
         If the service providers are dependent to some extent in external partners or suppliers, they cannot commit to meeting SLA target unless supplier´s performances underpin these targets. Contracts with external supplier are mandatory, in these contracts should reflect the need to ensure that all the targets with in underpinning are aligned with and support targets agreed in the SLAs.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="SLAMP.A4 - Monitor service performance against SLA">
      <description>
         This activity will monitor the provided services against to the agreed parameters in the SLA in the activity SLAMP.A2. Mechanisms to control potential deviations should be put in place.  This activity is repeated with the periodicity which is defined in the SLA
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="SLAMP.A5 – Produce service reports">
      <description>
         The SLA reporting mechanisms must be defined and agreed with the customer. The periodic reports should incorporate details of performance against all SLA targets. It is important for elaborating these reports to collect accurate information from all the areas and other processes and measured against the agreed business targets. During this activity, reports on the performance of the services should be produce,  this performance of the services should be checked against the SLA and  in case of any non-conformance, an information report should be produced and propagated to the affected parts.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="SLAMP.A6 Review SLAs and underpinning agreements">
      <description>
         All the SLAs and underpinning agreements must be kept updated. These reviews should ensure that the services covered and the targets for each are still relevant, and that nothing significant has changed that invalidates the agreement in any way. This activity should be carried out at least each time that major changes or incidence have been found.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
